<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Home</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nathankuik.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automated Mobile iOS &amp; Android Builds using Fastlane and CircleCI</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/automating-mobile-app-builds-releases/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/automating-mobile-app-builds-releases/</guid><description>Automated App Builds &amp;amp; Releases I was recently tasked with automating the iOS and Android build and releases at my work last month. We had some compliance checks coming up, and instead of making 2+ dev machines a part of the audit process, the decision was made to fully automate the build and release process.
After doing some initial digging, I realized that there was a bit more to it than I had first thought, primarily due to the fact that the current process involved a designated individual from each team doing a manual clean build and upload, using shared certificates and keys.</description></item><item><title>Terraformed AWS API Gateway Lambda Function with Custom Domain</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/terraform-aws-api-gateway-lambda/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/terraform-aws-api-gateway-lambda/</guid><description>API Gateway V1 (REST) vs. V2 (Websocket and HTTP) I was setting up a Lambda Function that sat behind a specific route of an API Gateway the other day at work, instead of setting up a microservice on a Kubernetes cluster and dealing with the ingress/deployment setup. While I was able to find specific pieces of this setup out there on the interwebs, I didn&amp;rsquo;t find an end-to-end solution that just worked &amp;ldquo;out of the box.</description></item><item><title>The Kubernetes Threshold</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/kubernetes-threshold/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/kubernetes-threshold/</guid><description>A Single Server Let’s imagine a small server running an application out in the wild. The application is small&amp;ndash;it requires only a backend server, a database, and some static frontend code&amp;ndash;but despite its size, the traffic on this server has been increasing in the last few weeks.
As the traffic continues to grow, response times grow slower and users begin complaining about the application’s slowness. Thankful that the application is seeing increased traffic, the main developer of the application uses a late night to increase CPU and memory on the server (a vertical scale), which succeeds without issue.</description></item><item><title>Fighting Burnout, Burnout Series Pt. 2</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/fighting-burnout/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 19:15:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/fighting-burnout/</guid><description>The second part of in my series on burnout: Fighting Burnout.</description></item><item><title>What Actually is Burnout, Burnout Series Pt. 1</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/what-actually-is-burnout/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 19:15:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/what-actually-is-burnout/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve begun a series on burnout and what we can do about. The first part of the series can be found here.</description></item><item><title>My Mandatory Junior Web Dev Post</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/my-mandatory-junior-web-dev-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 17:11:40 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/my-mandatory-junior-web-dev-post/</guid><description>My post about starting out in the world as a junior dev is on Medium here</description></item><item><title>Danish Harm Reduction</title><link>https://nathankuik.com/posts/danish-harm-reduction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 19:15:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nathankuik.com/posts/danish-harm-reduction/</guid><description>I wrote an article highlighting the effectiveness of harm reduction for the substance use and mental health blog The Fix, and it can be found here.</description></item></channel></rss>